Guide to the Medical Center Public Relations records, 1913-1999 RG0045
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1975-1983; RG0045 Series 5; 3 Linear feet
  This series contains photographs. The material dates from 1975-83. The subjects of these images are faculty, staff, and events. Some of the more noteworthy subjects include Ben Aaron, Paul Adkins, Luther Brady, Frank Miller, James Watts, the The George Washington University Family Clinic, Ross Hall construction in July 1978, Ronald Reagan's hospital room, James Brady leaving the hospital, hospital week, and nurses.
  - McGowan, Larry, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - Dr. Elgart, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.2)
  - Dr. John Mermel, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
  - Lipid research, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.4)
  - Medical School Pary, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.5)
  - Disaster Drill, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.6)
  - Dr. Elgert, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.7)
  - Kaufman, Ronald, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.8)
  - Myers, Louise, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.9)
  - Coit, Alan, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - Kidney Perfusion Machine, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.11)
  - Kuwait Visitors, 08/1975 (Box 1, Folder 1.12)
  - Hospital Week Exhibit, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.13)
  - Architects' Model of the Duncan Pavilion, 06/1975 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Gastroenterology Room, 06/1975 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Dr. Dobbins, 06/1975 (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Dr. Canter, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - Jacobson, Helen, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Intensive Care Unit, 02/1987 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Washington Circle, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.2)
  - Perlin, Stern, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.3)
  - Beaumont, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.4)
  - Trujillo, Nelson, 06/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.5)
  - Dr. Robins, 06/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.6)
  - Dr. Dew, 06/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.7)
  - Martin Abels, Retirement, 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 3.8)
  - Spanish Senior Center, 07/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.9)
  - Footer, Marvin, 03/1987 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Fetal Medical Symposium, 06/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.11)
  - Brody, David, 06/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.12)
  - House of Officer's Orientation, 06/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.13)
  - Simpson Retirement, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.14)
  - Dr. Grodin, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.15)
  - Dr. Dodek, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.16)
  - G.W. Medical Center, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3.17)
  - CINE Award Banquet, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4.1)
  - Sadat Visit, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
  - Clowning in the Snow, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4.3)
  - Loube, Samuel, 02/1987 (Box 1, Folder 4.4)
  - Radiology Nurses, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
  - Wasserman Gift, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5.2)
  - Dr. Pizzali, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5.3)
  - Dr. Elliot, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5.4)
  - Wasserman Cardiac Imaging, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5.5)
  - Shulman, Joe M.D., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6.1)
  - Stillman, Robert, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6.2)
  - Genetic Couseling, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6.3)
  - Stillman, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6.4)
  - IVP March, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6.5)
  - Bloom, Meryl, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6.6)
  - Follies, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7.1)
  - Gail Povas M.D., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7.2)
  - Reagan visits Ed Rollins, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7.3)
  - Ed Rollins, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7.4)
  - Philips E. Retirement Party, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
  - Birnbaum, 11/1982 (Box 1, Folder 8.2)
  - Holinghead, 11/1982 (Box 1, Folder 8.3)
  - White P. Dr., Rheumatologist, 11/1982 (Box 1, Folder 9.1)
  - Fitness Center, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9.2)
  - White, Patience M.D., 11/1982 (Box 1, Folder 9.3)
  - The Arthur Horwitz Memorial, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10.1)
  - Rich Ellis, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10.2)
  - Dr. Dew, 06/1977 (Box 1, Folder 10.3)
  - Dr. Gorman, 03/1975 (Box 1, Folder 11.1)
  - Intern President, 03/1975 (Box 1, Folder 11.2)
  - Procurement and Supply, Ross Hall, 03/1975 (Box 1, Folder 11.3)
  - Landon Banfield and Medical, 03/1975 (Box 1, Folder 11.4)
  - G.W.U. Medical P.R., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11.5)
  - Byers, Cynthia, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11.6)
  - Hurley, Pat, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11.7)
  - Portnoi, Valery Geriatiric Med., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12.1)
  - Kzufner, Cooper, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12.2)
  - Himmelfeld Foundation, 02/1982 (Box 1, Folder 12.3)
  - Taiwanese Visitors, 02/1982 (Box 1, Folder 12.4)
  - Mailey, Janet, 02/1982 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Ed Renauer, 02/1982 (Box 1, Folder 13.1)
  - Drenkard, Karen, 02/1982 (Box 1, Folder 13.2)
  - Webster G. Thomas, 02/1982 (Box 1, Folder 13.3)
  - Moody, Terry, 04/1982 (Box 1, Folder 14.1)
  - Mills, Mitchel, 04/1982 (Box 1, Folder 14.2)
  - Dr. Isaacson, 05/1982 (Box 1, Folder 14.3)
  - Baby birth, 02/1982 (Box 1, Folder 15.1)
  - Ratner, Robert (Endocrinology), 08/1982 (Box 1, Folder 15.2)
  - Tucker, Edward, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16.1)
  - Shaffer, Michael, 05/1982 (Box 1, Folder 16.2)
  - Women's Board, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16.3)
  - Dr. Becker, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16.4)
  - Dr. Goyne, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16.5)
  - Koshin, Ron, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16.6)
  - Student, 3rd Grade, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17.1)
  - Tucker, Edward, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17.2)
  - Repalwar, Ralph, 07/1982 (Box 1, Folder 17.3)
  - Dr. Leary, 07/1982 (Box 1, Folder 17.4)
  - Dr. Kaufman, 07/1982 (Box 1, Folder 18.1)
  - Watt, James, 07/1982 (Box 1, Folder 18.2)
  - Bowles O'Leary, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18.3)
  - Becker, Arthur, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19.1)
  - Flax, Richard, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19.2)
  - Surgery Open House, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19.3)
  - Dr. Goldstein, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19.4)
  - Dr. Steinberg, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19.5)
  - Charles, John, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19.6)
  - Dr. Yochelson, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19.7)
  - Caprim Noise, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19.8)
  - Hospital Week, undated (Box 1, Folder 20.1)
  - People Who Spent 25 Years at G.W., undated (Box 1, Folder 20.2)
  - Donald Glew, 04/1975 (Box 1, Folder 20.3)
  - Dennis 0'Leary, undated (Box 1, Folder 20.4)
  - Glew, Donald, undated (Box 1, Folder 20.5)
  - Letsky, Bill, undated (Box 1, Folder 21.1)
  - Anatomy Faculty, undated (Box 1, Folder 21.2)
  - Health Fair, undated (Box 1, Folder 21.3)
  - Dr. Pierpont, 30 Years at G.W., undated (Box 1, Folder 21.4)
  - Hospital 30th Birthday, 05/1972 (Box 1, Folder 21.5)
  - Dr. Gorman, Therapy, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 21.6)
  - Trustees Tour, 1987-1979 (Box 1, Folder 22.1)
  - Giorgio, Joseph, 09/1979 (Box 1, Folder 22.2)
  - Goldstein, Gandel, 12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 22.3)
  - Health Call, 01/1979 (Box 1, Folder 22.4)
  - Mullins Citation Award, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 22.5)
  - Boren, Nova, 06/1978 (Box 1, Folder 22.6)
  - Sirulnik, Eric, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22.7)
  - Diagnosis and Therapeutic Block, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22.8)
  - Gorman, Patrick, 04/1979 (Box 1, Folder 23.1)
  - Donald, P., 04/1979 (Box 1, Folder 23.2)
  - Larsen, John, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23.3)
  - Canter, Jerome, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23.4)
  - Eye St. Mall Dedication, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23.5)
  - George Bust Dedication1980 (Box 1, Folder 23.6)
  - Goldstein, A Ph.D., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23.7)
  - Miller, Harry M.D., 05/1980 (Box 1, Folder 23.8)
  - Gollers, Herbert Lab 100 Years Old, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23.9)
  - Follies, 04/1975 (Box 1, Folder 23.1)
  - Brady, James, 11/1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.1)
  - Reagan Hospital Room, 04/1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.2)
  - Tsangaris, N. M.D., 03/1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.4)
  - Aaron, Ben M.D., 03/1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.5)
  - McCarthy, Tim Press Conference, 04/1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.6)
  - Himmelfarb Portraits, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.7)
  - Bowles/Kiemonitz, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.8)
  - Chinese visitors, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.9)
  - Hollingsneld, A., 11/1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.1)
  - Adkins, Paul M.D., 11/1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.2)
  - Marguis, Jeanne, 11/1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.3)
  - Philson M.D., 02/1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.4)
  - Adams Morgan Clinic, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.5)
  - Dr. Philson, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.6)
  - Zolar, Mary, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.7)
  - Silver, Harold M.D., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.8)
  - Dr. Dew, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25.9)
  - 3Preemie Party, 11/1982 (Box 1, Folder 26.1)
  - Food Service Open House, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.2)
  - Dr. Silverstein, 07/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.3)
  - Dr. Borenstein, 07/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.4)
  - Jarkiewicz, Linola, 07/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.5)
  - Pisner Press Conf., 07/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.6)
  - Epstein/O'Leary, 07/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.7)
  - Gross, Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 26.8)
  - Dr. Snell, 07/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.9)
  - Dr. Coackley, 05/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.1)
  - Parker, John, 05/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.11)
  - Parker, Sue Nurse, 05/1983 (Box 1, Folder 26.12)
  - Protritis, Gusak, 12/1977 (Box 1, Folder 27.1)
  - Keller, Robert R, 01/1978 (Box 1, Folder 27.2)
  - Allied Health Workshop, 06/1978 (Box 1, Folder 27.3)
  - US Navy, 01/1978 (Box 1, Folder 27.4)
  - Harvey Ammerman, 01/1987 (Box 1, Folder 27.5)
  - Cassidy, Marie, 02/1978 (Box 1, Folder 27.6)
  - Dance Class, 11/1977 (Box 1, Folder 28.1)
  - Coleman, Roy, 11/1977 (Box 1, Folder 28.2)
  - Dr. Lovine, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28.3)
  - Lewis, Wilbur, 12/1977 (Box 1, Folder 28.4)
  - Coleman and Edelstein, 12/1977 (Box 1, Folder 28.5)
  - St. Mary's Groundbreaking, 10/1977 (Box 1, Folder 29.1)
  - Duncan Pavilion, 10/1977 (Box 1, Folder 29.2)
  - Blade Memorial Service, 11/1977 (Box 1, Folder 29.3)
  - Dr. Paul Corso, 09/1977 (Box 1, Folder 30.1)
  - G.W.U. Hospital, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30.2)
  - Metro: First Rider, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30.3)
  - Frensilli, Frederick, 10/1977 (Box 1, Folder 30.4)
  - Duncan Pavilion, 10/1977 (Box 1, Folder 31.1)
  - Hawkins, 10/1977 (Box 1, Folder 31.2)
  - Thompson, Charles, 11/1977 (Box 1, Folder 31.3)
  - Dr. William, 09/1977 (Box 1, Folder 32.1)
  - McKelway, M.D., 09/1977 (Box 1, Folder 32.2)
  - Hemophilia Center, 10/1977 (Box 1, Folder 32.3)
  - Internegs Duncan Pavilion, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 32.4)
  - Wiener, Jerry, 08/1977 (Box 1, Folder 33.1)
  - Volunteer Ficker, 09/1977 (Box 1, Folder 33.2)
  - Fisher, A., 09/1977 (Box 1, Folder 33.3)
  - White, Mary Retirement, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 33.4)
  - Ott, John, 08/1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Tradwell, Carlton, 08/1977 (Box 1, Folder 35.1)
  - McCarty, Carl C., 08/1977 (Box 1, Folder 35.2)
  - Peggy, Milton, 07/1977 (Box 1, Folder 35.3)
  - Berenson, Robert A., 08/1977 (Box 1, Folder 36.1)
  - Sidransky, Herschel, 07/1977 (Box 1, Folder 36.2)
  - METRO Opening, Foggy Bottom, 01/1977 (Box 1, Folder 36.3)
  - Otolaryngologgy, 05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 37.1)
  - Hospital Week Photo, 04/1977 (Box 1, Folder 37.2)
  - Geelhoed Tranplant Symposium, 05/1977 (Box 1, Folder 37.3)
  - Miller, Frank, 05/1977 (Box 1, Folder 37.4)
  - Ommaya Operation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 38.1)
  - Terry, Mary, 09/1977 (Box 1, Folder 38.2)
  - Macht, Steven M.D., 12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 39.1)
  - Food Service, 01/1984 (Box 1, Folder 39.2)
  - Frank, M.D., 01/1984 (Box 1, Folder 39.3)
  - Dr. Gordun, 01/1984 (Box 1, Folder 39.4)
  - British Delegation, 12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 40.1)
  - Knoll, Stanley M.D., 12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 40.2)
  - Emergency Medicine, 12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 40.3)
  - Plague, 12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 40.4)
  - Japanese Visitors, 08/1976 (Box 1, Folder 41.1)
  - Grey's Budd, 07/1976 (Box 1, Folder 41.2)
  - NBC's Bicentential Baby, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 41.3)
  - Hoof J., Elizabeth, 07/1976 (Box 1, Folder 41.4)
  - Sheagren, John, 07/1975 (Box 1, Folder 41.5)
  - Baranski, Joseph, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 41.6)
  - Mermel, John, 03/1976 (Box 1, Folder 42.1)
  - Dr. Molinary, 03/1976 (Box 1, Folder 42.2)
  - Bowie, Roland, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 42.3)
  - Klopp, Calvin, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 42.4)
  - Lee, Fidball, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 42.5)
  - Reagan and his hospital nurses, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24.3)
  - Adkins, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 43.1)
  - Lackitz, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 43.2)
  - Weingold, Allan, undated (Box 1, Folder 43.3)
  - Hospital Construction, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 44.1)
  - Crowell, Jack, 02/1976 (Box 1, Folder 44.2)
  - Zevallo's, Ann, 02/1976 (Box 1, Folder 44.3)
  - Garfinkel, Joel, 03/1976 (Box 1, Folder 44.4)
  - D.C Medical Society, 09/1975 (Box 1, Folder 45.1)
  - Cooper, Irving, 09/1975 (Box 1, Folder 45.2)
  - Palmer, Richard, 09/1975 (Box 1, Folder 45.3)
  - Dr. Watts, 09/1975 (Box 1, Folder 45.4)
  - Dr. Mermel, 09/1975 (Box 1, Folder 45.5)
  - Houten, Van, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45.6)
  - Alumni Association Party, 05/1975 (Box 1, Folder 46.1)
  - Himmelfarb Library, 06/1975 (Box 1, Folder 46.2)
  - Geelhoed, Glenn, 06/1975 (Box 1, Folder 46.3)
  - Dr. Ronald, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 46.4)
  - Deatley, Gaig, 10/1976 (Box 1, Folder 47.1)
  - Brady, Luther, 01/1977 (Box 1, Folder 47.2)
  - Miller, Frank, 11/1976 (Box 1, Folder 48.1)
  - Alumni Reception, 11/1976 (Box 1, Folder 48.2)
  - Mrs. Davison, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 48.3)
  - Dr. Snell, 11/1976 (Box 1, Folder 48.4)
  - Medical Student, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 49.1)
  - Swine Flu Vaccination, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 49.2)
  - C.C.U I.C. Nursery, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Radiology Retirement Party, 08/1976 (Box 1, Folder 51.1)
  - Waters, Budd, 09/1976 (Box 1, Folder 51.2)
  - Gray, Budd, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 52.1)
  - NBC Bicentennial Baby, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 52.2)
  - Bowie, Roland, 06/1976 (Box 1, Folder 52.3)
  - Mullin, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 52.4)
  - Dr. Sank, 04/1977 (Box 1, Folder 53.1)
  - Dr. Swanson, 04/1977 (Box 1, Folder 53.2)
  - Calling, George, 03/1977 (Box 1, Folder 53.3)
  - Washington Hilton Donation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 54.1)
  - Quads Photos, 02/1977 (Box 1, Folder 54.2)
  - Kane King Society, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 54.3)
  - Gyn B., 03/1977 (Box 1, Folder 54.4)
  - Van Leuvan, Linda, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 55.1)
  - Body Scan, 02/1977 (Box 1, Folder 55.2)
  - Caniglia, Laureen, 12/1976 (Box 1, Folder 56.1)
  - AV Malformation, 05/1977 (Box 1, Folder 56.2)
  - Halbersteem, 01/1977 (Box 1, Folder 56.3)
  - O' Leary, 11/1981 (Box 1, Folder 57.1)
  - AAMCPR Award, 11/1981 (Box 1, Folder 57.2)
  - White P., Dr., 11/1981 (Box 1, Folder 57.3)
  - Shea, John, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 58.1)
  - Shock/Trauma Symposium, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 58.2)
  - Myers Bill, 05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 58.3)
  - Dow, Robert, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 59.1)
  - Hospital Week Photo, 04/1978 (Box 1, Folder 59.2)
  - Dr. Davies, 05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 60.1)
  - Chef Braxton's Retirement, 07/1978 (Box 1, Folder 60.2)
  - Security System, 07/1978 (Box 1, Folder 60.3)
  - Ross Hall Construction, 07/1978 (Box 1, Folder 60.4)
  - Casey, Andrea & Jeff, 08/1978 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Russian Scientists, 09/1978 (Box 1, Folder 62.1)
  - Baer, Alfred, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 62.2)
  - Dr. Zimmerman, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 62.3)
  - Chinese Physicians Visit, 11/1978 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Allen, Monsac, 11/1978 (Box 1, Folder 64.1)
  - Schlein, Paul, 12/1978 (Box 1, Folder 64.2)
  - Dalthrop, Rick, 01/1979 (Box 1, Folder 64.3)
  - St. Andre, Christine, 01/1979 (Box 1, Folder 65.1)
  - Thompson, Annne, 01/1979 (Box 1, Folder 65.2)
  - Health Watch Patient, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 65.3)
  - Normal Isaacson, 01/1979 (Box 1, Folder 65.4)
  - Minnie Morris Retirement Party, 03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 65.5)
  - Ein, Daniel, 03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 66.1)
  - University Hospital, 03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 66.2)
  - Olem, Hoed Geel, 09/1980 (Box 1, Folder 67.1)
  - Birnhaum, Philip, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 67.2)
  - Hugo, Rizzol, 07/1980 (Box 1, Folder 67.3)
  - Howard, Lewis, 05/1980 (Box 1, Folder 68.1)
  - G.W Family Planning Clinic, 05/1979 (Box 1, Folder 68.2)
  - Warren, Claire, 03/1980 (Box 1, Folder 68.3)
  - Cafeteria Opening, 03/1980 (Box 1, Folder 68.4)
  - William, Jerry, 07/1979 (Box 1, Folder 69.1)
  - Carre, Jack, 07/1979 (Box 1, Folder 69.2)
  - Dr. Valaske, 08/1979 (Box 1, Folder 69.3)
  - Ross Portrain & Cardiology Symp., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 69.4)
  - Cardiac Rehabilitation, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 69.5)
  - Paula, Cox, 08/1979 (Box 1, Folder 69.6)
  - Hospital Week, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 69.7)
  - Willinger, Karl, 02/1979 (Box 1, Folder 70.1)
  - Patient Safety Committee Award, 02/1979 (Box 1, Folder 70.2)
  - Hospital Employee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 70.3)
  - Bloedorn Dean, 03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 70.4)
  - Himmel Farb Library, 03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 70.5)
  - Michael, Mark, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Suzan, Ruffalo, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 72.1)
  - Dowell, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 72.2)
  - Reynolds, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 72.3)
  - Jackson, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 72.4)
  - Davis, Margaret, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 72.5)
  - Boyd, Burn, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 72.6)
  - Jeno, Wendell, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 73.1)
  - Giordano, Joseph, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 73.2)
  - Jenkins, Robert, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 73.3)
  - Hospital Building, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 74.1)
  - Duncan, Andrew, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 74.2)
  - Tsung, Cheng Dr., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 74.3)
  - Ambassador Zhang's Visit, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 74.4)
  - Allied Health, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 74.5)
  - Don Health, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 74.6)
  - Historical Internegs used in 1976 Hospital Week, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 74.7)
  - Dr. Lean, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 75.1)
  - Steven Muller, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 75.2)
  - Gallo Robert, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.1)
  - Silversmith in Morocco, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.2)
  - Butler, Robert, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.3)
  - Al Doory, Yousel, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.4)
  - Kidney Transplant, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.5)
  - Beaumont Society Research, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.6)
  - Mc. Cullars, George, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.7)
  - Chopivsky, Peter, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.8)
  - King, Kane, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.9)
  - Surgery Urology, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.1)
  - Keshishian, Dr. John, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76.11)
  - Dog Surgery - Dr. Hoges, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 77.1)
  - Animal Surgery Dr. L. Kazloff, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 77.2)
  - Party Central Service, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 77.3)
  - Student Health Service, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 77.4)
  - Resident in Hospital, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 77.5)
  - Center for Family Research, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 77.6)
  - New Bowling Therapy, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 77.7)
  - Earl, Dr. Southerland, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 77.8)
  - Russel, Dr. Mautily, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.1)
  - Knavs, Dr. Williams, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.2)
  - Affront, Dr. Louis, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.3)
  - Newcity Earle, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.4)
  - Hendrick, Jim, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.5)
  - Foote, Jackie, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.6)
  - Roger, Stevens, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.7)
  - Family Care Conference, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.8)
  - Langford Lester LTOK, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.9)
  - Klimcheck, Jim, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.1)
  - Jenkins, Ed, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.11)
  - Martin, Pat, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.12)
  - Dr. Jorge, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.13)
  - Correl, Carla, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.14)
  - Stravely, Dr. Robert, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78.15)
  - Bioelectronics Laboratory, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.1)
  - Shaffer, Michael, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.2)
  - Anatomy Museum, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.3)
  - Zook, Dr. Bernard, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.4)
  - Viccohn Dr. Vis, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.5)
  - Pakistan Doctors, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.6)
  - Mc Gowan, Larry, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.7)
  - ICV Coronary Bypass Operation, undated (Box 2, Folder 79.8)
  - Corso, Dr. Paul, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.9)
  - Mercer Barbara, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.1)
  - Klingen, Maies, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79.11)
  - Lipid Research, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 80.1)
  - Jewish Community Centre, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 80.2)
  - 1000th EMI Patient, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 80.3)
  - Rockoff Dr, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 80.4)
  - Alpert, K. Louis, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 81.1)
  - Mullins, Edward, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 81.2)
  - Dr. Sean, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 82.1)
  - O' Kelly Portrait, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 82.2)
  - Beer Party, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 82.3)
  - Chinese Embassador, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 83.1)
  - Jerez Dr. Jose Alvaro, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 83.2)
  - Herbert, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 83.3)
  - Baral, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 83.4)
  - Glew, Dr. Donald, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 84.1)
  - White, Dr., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 84.2)
  - O' Leary, Dennis, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 84.3)
  - Geelhoed, Dr. Glenn, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 84.4)
  - Arling, Dr. Bryan, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 84.5)
  - Cresswell, Dr. Diane, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 84.6)
  - Kidney Transplant, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 85.1)
  - Semerdjian, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 85.2)
  - Geelhoed, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 85.3)
  - Hoge Eugene & James, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 85.4)
  - Columbia Hospital for Women, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 85.5)
  - Adkins, Paul, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 85.6)
  - Glenn John, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86.1)
  - Dr. Kauffman, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86.2)
  - Goldstein, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86.3)
  - EMI Tech & Fake Patient, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86.4)
  - Exterior Warwick, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86.5)
  - Goller, Dr. Herbert, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86.6)
  - Martin, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86.7)
  - McGowan, Dr. Larry, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86.8)
  - Lynch, Dr. Alpert, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 87.1)
  - Dr. Coakley, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 87.2)
  - Kayser, Dr. Elmer, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 87.3)
  - Himmelfarb Library, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 87.4)
  - Medical Student Registration, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 88.1)
  - Edwardsin Dr. Gordon, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 88.2)
  - Transporter, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 88.3)
  - Dr. O' Leary, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 88.4)
  - Kane King Speech and Dinner, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 89.1)
  - EMI Scanner, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 89.2)
  - Chamberlain, C. Shead, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 89.3)
  - Kauffman, Dr. Donald, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 89.4)
  - Parrish, Dr. Alvin, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 89.5)
  - Presentation of Sony Equip, undated (Box 2, Folder 89.6)
  - Bowles, Dr. Thompson, undated (Box 2, Folder 89.7)
  - Bowie, Roland, undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Longtime Wokers, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.1)
  - Kenmore, Dr. Peter, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.2)
  - Some Follies, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.3)
  - Jackson, Dr. Michael, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.4)
  - Peery, Dr. Thomas, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.5)
  - Geelford, Dr. Glenn, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.6)
  - Perry, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.7)
  - Alpert, Dr. Lewis, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.8)
  - Dobbins, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.9)
  - Dr. Brown, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91.1)
  - Medical School Pictures, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 92.1)
  - Holy Cross Affiliation, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 92.2)
  - Kane, King, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Washington Hospital Center, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 94.1)
  - Affiliation Agreement Signing, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 94.2)
  - Women's Board, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Zoo, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Dedication Photos, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Faculty Misc, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Luther Rice Society, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Stuart, Gilbert Portrait, undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Watts, Dr. James, undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Burett, undated (Box 2, Folder 12.1)
  - Roberts, Volinger, undated (Box 2, Folder 12.2)
  - Burus Building, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - VA Dean's Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Telephone 1977, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Historical, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16.1)
  - Gill, Chair, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16.2)
  - Glew, Dr. Donald, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16.3)
  - Golden Apple Awards, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16.4)
  - Himmelfarb Photo, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16.5)
  - Gorilla, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Watts, Freeman, undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Beachley, Ralph, undated (Box 2, Folder 19.1)
  - Calabrisi, Dr. Paul, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19.2)
  - Duncan Interneg, undated (Box 2, Folder 110.1)
  - Anesthesiology, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 110.2)
  - Pogye, Peggy, undated (Box 2, Folder 110.3)
  - Dr. John Parks, undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Dr. John Parks, undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Pebbles, undated (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Dr. John Parks, undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Medical Center history, 1980-1990; RG0045 Series 6; 6 Linear feet